What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm here to make the request with you.
أنا هنا لتقديم الطلب معك.
Then do you know
ثم هل تعرف
why I'm making this request?
لماذا أقدم هذا الطلب؟
It's because I, Li Yan,
هذا لأنني ، لي يان ،
will marry no one but you, Lin Qianjin.
لن يتزوج أحد إلا أنت ، لين تشيانجين.
It's raining, let's hurry.
إنها تمطر ، دعنا نسرع.
Qianjin.
تشيانجين.
This is my decision alone.
هذا هو قراري وحده.
Because I've found the one to spend my life with.
لأنني وجدت الشخص الذي يقضي حياتي معه.
I'm willing to protect her for a lifetime.
أنا على استعداد لحمايتها مدى الحياة.
In this world,
في هذا العالم ،
whatever she wants, whatever she likes,
كل ما تريد ، كل ما تحبه ،
I'll find it for her.
سأجده لها.
No matter where she goes,
لا يهم إلى أين تذهب ،
whether it's
سواء كان ذلك
wandering the world,
يتجول في العالم ،
or returning to the countryside,
أو العودة إلى الريف ،
or even the hometown
أو حتى مسقط رأسها
she talks about,
تتحدث عن ،
I'll give up everything
سأتخلى عن كل شيء
to go with her.
للذهاب معها.
I will marry no one but you.
لن أتزوج أحد إلا أنت.
My resolve will never change.
حل بلدي لن يتغير أبدا.
This is probably the most touching thing
ربما هذا هو الشيء الأكثر لمس
you, this blockhead, have ever said.
أنت ، هذا blockhead ، قد قلت من أي وقت مضى.
Why is it so hot?
لماذا الجو حار جدا؟
No.
لا.
You can't kneel.
لا يمكنك الركوع.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Come back with me.
أعود معي.
Li Yan.
لي يان.
Please listen, okay?
من فضلك اسمع ، حسنا؟
You really can't kneel anymore.
لا يمكنك حقًا الركوع بعد الآن.
You'll lose your life.
ستفقد حياتك.
I beg the city lord.
أتوسل إلى سيد المدينة.
Please let the two of us be together.
من فضلك دع اثنين منا يكونا معا.
Li Yan.
لي يان.
If you keep this up, you'll really die.
إذا واصلت هذا الأمر ، فسوف تموت حقًا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
No.
لا.
I can't.
لا أستطبع.
I can't leave.
لا أستطيع المغادرة.
If I leave,
إذا غادرت ،
everything will be gone.
كل شيء سوف يختفي.
Let's go, please?
دعنا نذهب من فضلك؟
Is fate playing tricks on us?
هل يلعب مصير الحيل علينا؟
Our ending
نهايتنا
was already decided long ago.
تم تحديده بالفعل منذ فترة طويلة.
Miss.
يفتقد.
City lord.
سيد المدينة.
Please listen to what I have to say.
من فضلك استمع إلى ما يجب أن أقوله.
Didn't you say
ألم تقل
that in this world
هذا في هذا العالم
you would give me whatever I wanted?
هل تعطيني كل ما أردت؟
But what I want
لكن ما أريده
is the position of the city lord's wife.
هو موقف زوجة الرب المدينة.
This is the one thing
هذا هو الشيء الوحيد
I can't give you.
لا أستطيع أن أعطيك.
If you can't give it to me,
إذا لم تتمكن من إعطائها لي ،
then go and marry your Princess Changle.
ثم اذهب وتزوج من الأميرة تشانغل.
Miss,
يفتقد،
you—
أنت-
do you even know what you're saying?
هل تعرف حتى ما تقوله؟
I'm very clear about why I came here.
أنا واضح جدًا حول سبب جئني إلى هنا.
Escort Commander Li back to his residence.
قائد المرافقة لي العودة إلى مقر إقامته.
Send for the royal physician.
إرسال للطبيب الملكي.
Make sure he receives proper treatment.
تأكد من أنه يتلقى العلاج المناسب.
Yes.
نعم.
Please rest assured, City Lord.
الرجاء مطمئن يا رب المدينة.
I will fulfill everything I have promised.
سأفي بكل شيء وعدت به.
I also ask the City Lord
أنا أيضا أسأل المدينة سيد
to keep your word.
للحفاظ على كلمتك.
I have promised to make a clean break with Li Yan
لقد وعدت بإنشاء استراحة نظيفة مع لي يان
and end things completely.
وإنهاء الأمور تماما.
So that he will willingly marry Princess Changle.
حتى يتزوج عن طيب خاطر الأميرة تشانغل.
I sincerely hope the City Lord
آمل مخلصًا سيدي المدينة
will pardon him for his grave disrespect.
سوف العفو عنه لعدم احترام القبر.
And ensure his safety for the rest of his life.
وضمان سلامته لبقية حياته.
Then, have you truly ended your feelings for him?
ثم ، هل انتهيت حقًا من مشاعرك تجاهه؟
I take my leave.
أنا آخذ إجازتي.
Miss
يفتقد
Brother Li Yan
الأخ لي يان
You're awake
أنت مستيقظ
Changle
تشانغلي
It's you
انها أنت
Of course it's me
بالطبع هذا أنا
Who else would worry about you like I do?
من سيقلقك كما أفعل؟
Let me check if your fever's gone down
اسمحوا لي أن أتحقق مما إذا كانت الحمى قد سقطت
Changle
تشانغلي
I'm fine now
أنا بخير الآن
You should go back
يجب أن تعود
We're about to get married soon
نحن على وشك الزواج قريبًا
You don't have to be so reserved
ليس عليك أن تكون محجوزًا جدًا
Between Changle and me
بين تشانغل وأنا
we're just like siblings
نحن مثل الأشقاء
nothing more
لا شيء أكثر
I know you don't want to marry me
أعلم أنك لا تريد الزواج مني
But I still can't understand
لكن ما زلت لا أستطيع أن أفهم
what's so good about Lin Qianjin
ما هو جيد جدًا في لين تشيانجين
She's the one who made you like this
هي التي جعلك هكذا
I'm the one who's been by your side, taking care of you
أنا الشخص الذي كان بجانبك ، يعتني بك
Changle
تشانغلي
You're a good person
أنت شخص جيد
But in my heart
لكن في قلبي
I've already had Lin Qianjin for a long time
لقد كان لدي بالفعل لين تشيانجين لفترة طويلة
I'm destined to let down your feelings, Changle
أنا مقدر لي أن نخذل مشاعرك ، تشانغل
The one Changle loves in this life
واحد تشانغل يحب في هذه الحياة
shouldn't be me
لا ينبغي أن أكون أنا
You're still thinking about Lin Qianjin
ما زلت تفكر في لين تشيانجين
The fate between you two has long run out
لقد نفد المصير بينكما منذ فترة طويلة
Now, the ones meant to be together are you and me
الآن ، من المفترض أن تكون معًا أنت ولي
Do you know
هل تعرف
she's now happily
هي الآن بسعادة
preparing for her wedding
تستعد لحفل زفافها
to become the city lord's wife
لتصبح زوجة الرب في المدينة
Miss
يفتقد
I have something to tell you
لدي شيء لأخبرك به
Li Sijun, you have trespassed into the City Lord's private residence.
Li Sijun ، لقد تعهدت في مقر الإقامة الخاصة بمدينة Lord.
If you’re not here to congratulate me,
إذا لم تكن هنا لتهنئتي ،
please show some respect and leave.
يرجى إظهار بعض الاحترام والمغادرة.
Miss
يفتقد
can you tell me
هل يمكن أن تخبرني
why?
لماذا ؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Didn't I make it very clear to you before?
ألم أوضح لك من قبل؟
I don't believe it.
أنا لا أصدق ذلك.
Then, Li Sijun,
ثم ، لي سيجون ،
was I wrong about you from the very beginning?
هل كنت مخطئا فيك منذ البداية؟
I’ve always been cruel and heartless.
لطالما كنت قاسياً وبلا قلب.
How could I ever truly care about anyone?
كيف يمكن أن أهتم حقًا بأي شخص؟
From start to finish,
من البداية إلى النهاية ،
you were nothing more than
لم تكن أكثر من
a pawn to help me become the City Lord’s wife.
بيدق لمساعدتي في أن أصبح زوجة الرب في المدينة.
Just a chess piece, that’s all.
مجرد قطعة شطرنج ، هذا كل شيء.
Miss
يفتقد
Did I do something wrong?
هل فعلت شيئًا خاطئًا؟
Or did the city lord force you?
أو هل دفعك رب المدينة؟
I told you before,
قلت لك من قبل ،
we would face everything together.
سوف نواجه كل شيء معًا.
You promised me.
لقد وعدتني.
We would enjoy all the romantic things together.
سوف نستمتع بكل الأشياء الرومانسية معًا.
In spring,
في الربيع ،
we would go for outings together.
كنا نذهب للنزهات معا.
And in summer,
وفي الصيف ،
we would jump into the pool and swim together.
كنا نقفز إلى المسبح ونسبح معًا.
In early winter,
في أوائل الشتاء ،
with the one you love,
مع الشخص الذي تحب ،
eat fried chicken together.
أكل الدجاج المقلي معًا.
Drink beer and eat fried chicken.
اشرب البيرة وتناول الدجاج المقلي.
These are all things you said.
هذه كلها الأشياء التي قلتها.
I'll take you away right now.
سآخذك بعيدا الآن.
Far away from this place.
بعيدا عن هذا المكان.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
No.
لا.
Come on, let's go.
تعال ، دعنا نذهب.
Let go.
اتركه.
Was I not clear enough with you?
لم أكن واضحا معك؟
Do you still not understand?
هل ما زلت لا تفهم؟
From beginning to end,
من البداية إلى النهاية ،
I was lying to you.
كنت أكذب عليك.
Every minute I spent with you,
كل دقيقة قضيتها معك ،
every second,
كل ثانية ،
I felt miserable.
شعرت بائسة.
Go.
يذهب.
I'm not leaving.
أنا لا أغادر.
Let go.
اتركه.
We once went through life and death together.
ذهبنا مرة واحدة من خلال الحياة والموت معا.
I won't let you go.
لن أسمح لك بالرحيل.
Let go.
اتركه.
I don't believe what you said. I don't believe it.
لا أصدق ما قلته. أنا لا أصدق ذلك.
Let me ask, in Nanling City,
اسمحوا لي أن أسأل ، في مدينة نانلينج ،
which woman
أي امرأة
doesn't want to become the city lord's wife?
لا تريد أن تصبح زوجة رب المدينة؟
Since the city lord favors me,
منذ أن تفضلني رب المدينة ،
that is the blessing I deserve.
هذه هي البركة التي أستحقها.
You can't possibly be naive enough to think
لا يمكنك أن تكون ساذجًا بما يكفي للتفكير
I would give up the position of city lord's wife
أود أن أتخلى عن منصب زوجة سيتي لورد
to be with someone like you,
لتكون مع شخص مثلك ،
a mere guard, right?
مجرد حارس ، أليس كذلك؟
As for Li Sijun,
أما بالنسبة للي سيجون ،
I advise you to quickly marry Princess Changle
أنصحك أن تتزوج بسرعة الأميرة تشانغل
to put an end to the rumors about us.
لوضع حد للشائعات عنا.
You should go.
يجب أن تذهب.
Then what about this—
ثم ماذا عن هذا -
this—
هذا-
Why did you personally
لماذا شخصيا
sew this sachet for me and give it to me back then?
خياطة هذا الكيس لي وأعطه لي في ذلك الوقت؟
If I hadn't found it,
إذا لم أجدها ،
would you have just abandoned it?
هل كنت قد تخليت للتو؟
I treasure everything you gave me.
أنا أعز كل شيء أعطيته لي.
I was just afraid you would die.
كنت خائفًا فقط من أنك ستموت.